(3. Today's the Opportunity)
It's the cheapest today.
Must a war start today?
- It's cheap today.
- It's because...
- We won't start the war.
- Tomorrow...
It makes sense for them to pay for war...
and start a war.
If we fail to make a deal,
we have to run right away
to start a war with Team Red today.
This is what I think.
That is, if we fail to make a deal.
If those two teams join forces,
we're doomed.
I brought it up first.
It was my idea.
We had to go to war.
If we are to go to war once now or later,
we must strike first.
If war breaks out,
it was written that
the side with more numbers...
would have an advantage.
So I thought it would be a good idea
to be on good terms with Team White.
- Hello.
Hi.
Hello.
For various reasons...
including the war announcement,
I thought we needed to...
- talk about our needs.
- Right.
We must stay alive...
- for our money to be meaningful.
- Right.
We must have money
for our lives to have meaning.
The reason for contacting you
was based on these needs.
First of all,
we're curious about your thoughts.
Would you want to form an alliance?
Or if you wish to avoid going to war,
will you keep things peaceful?
This is our direction.
It will be inevitable for us
to have our members eliminated...
due to limited lives.
We wish to live in peace
before that moment comes.
We don't want to make sacrifices.
What are your thoughts?
Do you have plans
to start a war in advance?
This is something
we have different opinions on.
- You have different opinions?
- We have different opinions.
(War)
(Peace)
What do you think is the advantage...
of starting a war in advance?
The fee for going to war...
- It can get more expensive?
- can get more expensive.
A loss was inevitable,
and that was based on the current price.
Whether that will get reduced
or increased over time,
I believe that wasn't...
explained to us in detail.
For us to reduce the damage
all of us might go through...
and to leave this place
with the biggest amount of money,
starting a war quickly
might be the answer.
We will lose people anyway...
- and if that's from the opposing team,
- Right.
you wish to secure...
- a greater amount of prize money, right?
- Right.
Everyone will suffer
the least damage at this point.
The fee for going to war...
- will get revealed first.
- Right.
The value of the diamonds at that point...
gets decided by us.
The rule states that it's based on
the value of diamonds...
- when the fee is paid.
- Right.
- So even if the fee...
- It's based on the number of diamonds.
becomes 30 diamonds from 15 diamonds,
- We can change the value.
- we can change...
the actual value in reality.
Before war breaks out,
we can change the value of the currency.
- We can lower the price like that.
- I see.
If we are to join forces,
- we can minimize our loss.
- Right.
We have that ability.
If we decide to work together,
we will be 9 against 3.
- We'll be greater in number.
- That's a big advantage.
- Right.
Actually, later on,
we will produce a lot more,
and if we have more things
in our possession,
- the value of half becomes much bigger.
- It becomes much bigger.
We believe a greater war will come...
if we decide to hold off on going to war.
If we are going to go to war anyway,
I thought it might be better for us
to secure peace instead.
But let's say we do go to war early.
There's no guarantee
that a second war will not break out.
Right. Let's say a war breaks out.
Our war deterrent
is issuing more diamonds.
If we do that a lot,
war will break out again.
- It will happen again and again.
- Right.
Why sit around
when the currency is so low?
It will become,
"Let's go to war to kill time."
The losing side...
- will have no more to lose.
- Right.
- They will start another war.
- That will be their only option.
- Right.
It will become, "One of us will die."
As if it's an arms race,
teams will continue to
pay the fee for war.
- That will keep reducing the prize money.
- Right.
Once a war breaks out,
everyone will suffer a loss.
There's no big reason
to start a war at this point.
- We still have time to...
- Then,
I think it's right for us
make at least a verbal contract.
- Why don't we write a contract?
- We should do that.
If we decide to join forces with Team Red,
it will be inevitable...
for both sides to suffer harm.
If it becomes 6 on 6, it will become
a bloody war for both sides.
What we can offer first...
- is a priority for trading with us.
- Right.
You can become the first ones...
- To negotiate with you?
- to negotiate with us.
- Before Team Red.
- Right.
- That's great.
- Thank you.
The priority for negotiating for lives...
will be great for us.
Issuing diamonds
will be inevitable for us.
We are still able to adjust the rate.
We believe we have no reason
to make diamonds worth close to nothing.
We can tell you that...
we will maintain the value of diamonds.
If we consider ourselves as one team,
until it is inevitable for us...
to eat our own members alive,
we will consider that our opponents
are outside of us.
The leaders should shake hands.
- We should shake hands.
- I'm sorry for having sweaty hands.
- This is quite sudden.
I wish us the best.
- The Town Hall Treaty.
The Town Hall Non-Aggression Treaty.
Fortunately,
Team White was friendly with us.
The six of them looked solid,
and that was why we wanted to
join forces with them.
But on second thought,
I belatedly thought that...
everything was designed
for us to be needed by them.
A 2-on-1 alliance was formed.
"Should we kill off Team Red
except for one last member?"
This suggestion could have been made...
if we were to be cruel.
But if that happens,
our team will have a greater influence...
in the long term.
Well, 3 plus 1 will still only be 4.
After a war breaks out,
the teams in that alliance
will go to war again.
I believe it will become
White against Blue.
But we are greater in number.
That means we have the advantage.
I was surprised that
they wanted to join forces with us first.
It will be great for us
if they didn't think that far.
There's no such thing as trust here.
But I do want to make them trust me.
I hate the commission so much.
It's unreasonable for us.
They keep pushing us
to pay the commission,
- Right.
- and I can't stand it.
They should pay!
For every deal we've made,
we've paid the commission.
Well, it makes sense
to a certain extent...
as we're the ones
who are collecting the credits.
But if this keeps happening,
we have to pay the commission
for every deal we make.
They don't seem to know
how generous we are.
They will never think that way.
This is what Team Blue will be thinking.
"We're sharing life."
Hold on. I see stairs over there.
Is this Black's house?
(They spot Black's dormitory
that is secluded.)
Won't it be fine if we stay outside?
Right.
There was something I was obsessed with
after coming here.
It's the passcode on the wall.
Based on my deduction,
there seemed to be 1 code
in each of the 4 houses...
as there were four boxes.
I wanted to collect those codes.
(Rummaging)
- Oh, hello.
- Hello.
Hello.
We're here
to take a look at Black's house.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
There must be nothing here.
There's nothing here.
Well,
if there was a way to barge inside,
I would've gone in even if it cost me
all of my diamonds.
But there's a rule that we can't
enter someone else's dorm.
Maillard seems to be...
suspicious of everything.
It felt so scary.
- Gosh, Black's house.
- Black was home.
(Laughing)
You haven't answered any of
the skill development questions, right?
Oh, I still haven't answered any of them.
I was a madman.
Really?
Even when I went down earlier,
he seemed to be answering several of them.
I'd like to make a suggestion.
If I reveal the questions
of the other teams,
that will cause harm to them.
If we get the right answer?
I could instead offer...
not to answer Team Red's questions.
Having a skill...
could be a great advantage
at the negotiating table.
- This is what I think.
- Right.
I kept approaching them
with a stance of...
wanting to be Team Red's cooperator.
I tried my best to listen
to Maillard's words.
I solved questions with him...
and tried to win his favor.
We came here first...
after deciding on our priority.
We can't offer you a lot
as we don't have much.
I was wondering if you have
earned yourself a lot today.
Did you earn lives?
Well, what can I reveal?
- We are planning to reveal everything...
- As for us...
- about us.
- Really? Well, it's quite obvious.
- Right.
- It's obvious.
We made a deal for lives.
- The efficiency...
- It's different.
- I believe it will be very different.
- Right.
That is why we think...
you have earned a lot.
- It was quite hard.
- Harder than you thought?
The questions were quite hard for us.
We expected to earn a lot.
Anyway, we weren't able to
earn a lot today.
So you don't have many lives
to offer to us.
We don't have a lot...
- that can be traded off.
- You don't have a lot?
- How many are they in number?
- Actually...
The number of lives
we were willing to trade off...
- was two.
- Two.
- Oh, really?
- Well,
we thought you would've been able
to earn 3 or 4.
- No.
- That is impossible.
- It's impossible with our efficiency.
- Our efficiency is low.
- It's really bad for us.
- Ten questions were answered.
- But...
- You must've earned around two.
(Team White's actual output, 2 lives)
So all we can do...
is purchase however many you offer.
So, for today,
if we offer you two or more,
that will mean...
we will be losing one of ours.
But that will keep all six of you alive.
- Right.
- If we offer you two,
you will need two more tomorrow.
- We will produce more tomorrow.
- Right.
We will offer you two more
after earning them tomorrow.
If we fail to earn our lives,
- we will offer up what we have.
- Right.
- That sounds good.
- Tomorrow,
- we will secure two lives for you.
- We'll do that.
Sounds good.
- How much is each life?
- The price.
We didn't talk about the price of them.
- Yesterday, one life...
- Ten diamonds.
was worth 10 diamonds,
which is 10,000 dollars.
We'll be honest.
We didn't issue more diamonds.
- Right.
- The prices are the same now.
But after our deal yesterday,
I noticed that the other teams...
have a lot more of the prize money
split among the members.
They have the most.
(The members of Team White
have 14 diamonds each.)
You must've traded off around 50
to Team Red yesterday.
The prize money value for each of us...
is quite low,
so we decided to offer
half of what we offered yesterday.
If we plan to issue a lot of diamonds,
we can offer to trade off a lot.
- Well...
- We'll take some time...
- to discuss the price.
- Right.
Team White will be able to survive
until tomorrow...
even without our lives.
If we refuse to give them
our lives the next day,
war will break out inevitably.
To prevent war,
we must offer them our lives.
What's worth 1 day for them
will be worth 2 days for us.
That puts a lot more pressure on us.
But we need to get a bit more.
If we get two,
there's a big chance
someone will get eliminated from our team.
You saw them calculate
the exact number, right?
She said, "If we trade off two,"
"you will need two more tomorrow."
(Current lives of Team White: 8)
(Genie predicted the exact number.)
But if we get two,
we can all live today and tomorrow.
Are we going to secure
just enough to survive each day?
Without a single life saved up?
A person will make a sudden change
if there's no backup.
- Team Red might charge at us.
- Half price or...
- Ten?
- Fifteen?
We don't want to trigger them...
- when they're short on lives.
- Should we ask for 12?
- We should ask for 12.
- Right.
We made the decision quickly.
- We'll ask for 12.
- You'll ask for 12?
We were talking,
and it felt like we were dayflies.
Getting two lives now...
and securing two for tomorrow
is very different.
Through the productive activities,
you might not be able to earn a lot...
because the questions are too hard.
If that happens,
we might not be able to secure six lives.
We will feel a lot more relieved
- with just one more.
- That's right.
What we're asking for is for your team...
to trade off your future lives...
to secure our near future.
- I believe that will feel like a risk.
- This is our plea.
Are you willing to hold a meeting...
to discuss offering us
more than two lives?
- We'll move out again.
- Right.
- Here we go.
We'll have 4 left after spending 6 today.
- They will be able to drag us around.
- Right.
- Twelve is enough for today and tomorrow.
- That will make them...
- take control of our lives.
- We'll be dead after that.
We'll all die if they betray us.
If we produce two tomorrow,
- we need four more.
- Right.
But will they...
be able to earn four
by answering the questions?
- Right.
- They're a lot more lacking...
than we think.
I don't think offering them three
isn't a bad idea at this moment.
Should we ask for 20 diamonds
for 3 lives, then?
Will that be possible?
Ask for 20 diamonds for 3 lives?
- That's asking for one more.
- Right.
- We'll ask for 18 without changing it?
- First of all...
- Four?
- I'm sorry.
- But...
you'll be able to produce
at least one tomorrow.
At least one tomorrow.
- That's not true!
- That's not what it's like.
- It isn't certain for us.
- It's really tough for us.
- But 4 from us would be...
- But 4 from us...
- Is that too tough for you?
- To be honest,
that's nearly how many we earned today.
- I see.
- So...
You did really well.
(Team Blue's actual output, 5 lives)
We were willing to offer half of that.
As we want to be on the same track,
- we decided to offer three lives.
- Right. That sounds good.
- We'll proceed with that deal.
- Right.
- But it'll be 18 diamonds for 3 lives.
- It'll be 18 diamonds...
- for 3 lives.
- It'll be 18 diamonds?
- One will cost six diamonds.
- Sounds good.
- We'll go with that.
- Right.
That's a straightforward deal. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
We didn't have many diamonds left.
If we went with the same deal
we made yesterday,
we would have to issue
a lot more diamonds,
and that would greatly lower
the value of the diamonds.
We did well to persuade them with this.
We didn't get a lot from them.
But we earned their trust
because of their fear.
We weren't the ones who gave them fear.
They came to us out of fear.
We didn't even threaten them.
Even though they had the upper hand,
they came to us in a lower stance.
We earned a lot more from them mentally.
After earning five,
we only wanted to offer two...
excluding three of our lives.
Two didn't seem like a lot
even in our eyes.
Since they needed a lot of lives,
they might've said,
"Please give them to us."
"We'll give you a lot of our diamonds."
They might've begged us for them.
I tried to avoid those situations
as much as possible.
Three lives seemed okay to offer.
We agree with what you said.
We like solving questions.
Right.
- Should we move over there?
- Sure. Shall we?
You received
the skill development questions, right?
- Yes.
- We haven't solved them yet.
- We also haven't solved them.
- I think that team got it right.
- It's a bit...
Are the questions endless?
They said they got it wrong.
- Right.
They're still together.
They were together for a long time.
- There's something between them.
- Red and Black.
We're gathered together.
I'm sure this team is
wanted by them the most.
They might be waiting...
- to talk.
- Should we make them feel anxious?
- Thank you.
- Here they are.
Nice.
- There's one more.
- Two.
(All skill development questions
get revealed.)
- They're all the same.
- Yes.
We're just asking what you think.
The skill development questions.
The questions can be shared
between us, right?
- The questions can be shared.
- What do you think?
Since we have different answers?
- Right.
We won't reveal each of our benefits
to each other.
I think it'll be okay
to share the questions with each other.
Black will answer them first
if we don't get them.
- We have to pay him.
- Exactly.
The books that we have
seem to be different.
- We have six heads.
- Then...
- Right.
Do you remember the parts?
This was what it was for the key.
"That Monday, the tower built by greed
collapsed silently."
"From now on, if our country's culture
and economy..."
"goes beyond rapid growth
and reaches relaxation growth..."
This seems to be Black Monday
or the Oil Shock.
Right.
- This is...
- Right.
- certainly the IMF crisis.
I looked for answers in the books,
but it was too hard to guess. So this...
The answers might be
in each other's books.
- Right. We have different books.
- Right.
(Team Blue's books)
(Team Red's books)
Did you have a book called "Money"
in your dorm?
- I didn't check the books at all.
- Right.
I'll look through them.
For example, if we all have the same book,
I feel like the hint is in that book.
(The hint for the question
is hidden in the books?)
Could it be about finding the dates?
One hour into the trading session.
- Could it be written?
- They're having a long conversation.
- One hour went by.
- Right.
I'm not sure how we're supposed
to answer them.
Right. That's the problem.
This is what it says
if we answer the question.
We'll just share this with you.
It says it will be applied if we answer
the skill development question.
I wonder what this means.
"When the answer submitted is correct,"
"the skill development..."
"and the answer
will get applied right away."
What can be applied from this?
"Applied?"
It feels like something
that will actually bring a change.
- It sounds off.
- If it's...
something that will get applied,
I understood it to be something...
that will get applied to this community.
- It's an answer...
- Right.
- that can be applied to this community.
- That's what it is.
That's a huge hint. Thank you.
- Right.
- But it's so hard to figure out.
We didn't read the questions in detail.
It wasn't just about getting the right
to use a certain skill.
The answer will be applied to our world
as well.
These were the two key points.
It's not just a skill that gets developed.
Could it be a systematic word...
that can be applied to our community?
This might turn out to be
a significant part,
so I didn't want to share about it
with another team.
Salt went,
"There was this as well."
She shared everything I said.
(Genie)
"All right, then."
- Well...
- They all seem to be related.
It would be great to hear from Team Red.
Should we split up, then?
We'll talk to Black.
- Sounds good.
- What about our deal?
- Then...
- We must make our deal.
- We must do that now.
We'll make our deal first.
- Our leaders should move.
- We'll meet there.
- Let's meet again at night.
- Right.
They've agreed to make a deal.
You've agreed to make a deal.
- Yes. We'll complete our deal.
- Right.
Leader.
Should we wait to talk to Team Red?
Three of us should stay here.
Wait if they contact us first.
- And wait for...
- Get going first.
Okay.
What's something that occurs...
as soon as a skill is developed?
What would be interesting
if it were to get applied right now?
That's a good approach.
Gosh.
(Salt heads over to get the resources
as Team Blue's leader.)
What was it again?
"Market's Memory," "Fifty Things
That Made the Modern Economy,"
"What Did Scientists Do in the War?"
The word "war..."
is really scary.
I don't have to take all of them with me.
Without going to war,
I hope we can live in peace
with each other.
To be honest, there's a big chance
for Team White to have...
- the first one to get eliminated.
- We expected it to be us.
- Everyone would think that.
- Right.
That could happen.
Gosh. This is a big workout.
- It's exhausting, right?
- It's a big workout.
- We'll be back.
- We'll wait here.
We'll be back.
Gosh!
These can't go to waste.
- Oh, no!
- Hold on.
- Hold on!
That's how it'll be.
Gosh, it got spilled.
What a mess.
Thank you.
I became someone who threw out
money on the floor.
- This is worth so much.
- Gosh!
You look very rich. How nice.
I'm sure you won't,
but you might get worried
that I might steal it.
Thank you.
(Team White pays the one credit.)
You must go that way.
Right.
Why did you leave it there?
- This is Team White's side. I'm sorry.
- Right.
I must be stupid.
Out of the ones we have...
(Trade: 3 lives for 18 diamonds)
Must I show you like this?
No. There will be a check
once you submit them.
There will be a check?
- You must get it checked first.
- We're checking the submitted amount.
Please wait a moment.
A leader with experience feels different.
The trade has been completed.
Thank you.
It's hard to move back and forth...
as we're at the top.
But actually...
Will you not buy credits today?
We can't make decisions.
- We'll move over when she returns.
- We'll move with our leader.
Can't we just start talking now?
We have to talk to two teams.
- Please give us a moment.
- She went to make a trade.
I was surprised by
Team White's change of attitude.
They didn't seem to be in need of credits.
A trade with Team White
isn't necessary today.
There's an awareness that things are...
getting tougher for us.
The value of credits...
is only found in productive activities.
They can only be used for hints
and retries.
If we start saving up on them,
just two credits might be needed
for a trade for lives...
along with question answering.
Things have become quite awkward for us.
I don't want to give it to Black
all of a sudden.
- No.
- No. We can't be like that.
We can't be naive...
and trust only Team White.
- You're right about that.
- Right.
We'll talk to Black
as we've made a promise.
(Vector asked for a life in the morning.)
But we can't trade with each other.
I'll make a black market.
That's possible?
I don't know.
I'm going to give it a try.
This is my offer.
If you give me a life,
I'll provide you with the food you want
for two days.
Let's take everything now.
We must not get caught.
(Team Blue got food
for giving him a life.)
I wanted to wear something big
for a reason.
- You must give me a life.
- Of course.
If he opens the supermarket tomorrow,
everyone will know that
we gave him a life.
We should come up with an excuse.
How should we put it?
Actually,
all we did was...
to give him a life for food.
That's true,
but talking to Black...
after talking to Team White...
could be something
that could break their trust.
- That is what concerns me.
- Right.
Right.
We gave away a life after saying
we were short on lives.
Could we have a moment, Black?
(Team Blue asks for
a sudden meeting with Black.)
You are in need...
- of lives as well.
- Right.
It's a matter of life and death for them.
They're all complaining about
wanting more lives.
We're going,
"This is all we can give you."
But it's quite awkward to say,
"We got some food from Black..."
"and gave him a life."
- I don't know what to say.
- Well,
we're not saying
we're not going to give you a life.
- We'll give you a life,
- Right.
but when we do,
- There should be a cause.
- there should be a cause.
We're asking what we can do about this.
How does this sound?
"We made a promise that Black will not..."
"work on our skill development question."
After securing our safety,
we can say that Black
took that into consideration.
That might work.
She's a genius today.
But you have to...
- take part in this with us.
- That's right.
- Then,
- I think that's a good idea.
- I'll think it through before dinner.
- Right.
I'll see if it's a reasonable idea.
We'll meet after that.
- Right.
- Thank you.
I can survive for another day.
Could we have a conversation?
Should we? Sounds good.
- Are you busy?
- Gosh.
We have a lot of things to carry.
- Could we put back our things?
- Sure.
There's not much time left until dinner.
- I'll be quick.
- Okay.
See you later.
What can we talk about with Team Red?
It won't hurt to talk.
I did tell them...
we had to visit the dorm
to come up with a plan.
When we first talked to Team Blue,
they said they had too many things...
and will be back from their dorm.
That was when I realized...
they didn't want to sell their lives.
"What must we do for our lives?"
"Must we produce lives tomorrow?"
These talks began between us.
If we are to make things ideal for us,
we have to contact Team Red
when Team Blue is not around.
- We have to contact Team Red.
- Right.
This is our advantage
with our greater number.
If they are to start a war,
we can go, "Form an alliance with us."
The moment we betray them,
we can take the win.
We can earn their lives like that.
It's the same for us,
whether we win with one or the other.
It will be the same 6-on-3 fight...
after we win with any team.
The best thing...
is to persuade Team Blue or Team Red...
with, "We will help you
if you start a war."
- Right.
- That becomes a huge win for us.
"Even if you form an alliance
with the other team,"
"you will get destroyed in a war."
If the other two teams form an alliance,
we can issue a lot of diamonds...
and make a lot of weapons.
We can destroy them after that.
We can't trust Team White.
They sat with Team Red
for another conversation.
(They spotted Team Red and Team White
having a conversation.)
- What's funny is this.
- Right.
Blue wasn't able to produce
a lot of lives.
They only produced two.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Team Blue?
(Vector lies about their life output.)
We'll be able to produce more than them.
- We should produce lives tomorrow.
- Right.
Tell Team Blue...
- to stay out of our sight.
- Right. Shall we go for it?
Team Red will produce lives now!
We might be able to sell lives
if we do a good job.
Right.
- We should just...
- When you talk with them,
don't be like, "You only produced two."
- Don't point that out to them.
- Never.
- I have to get lives...
- from Team Blue as well.
- Understood.
Vector kept saying these phrases
starting from yesterday.
He started the conversation with,
"I'll only tell Team Red about this."
"Don't say this to anyone else."
"Team Blue was able to produce
only two lives."
"We won't be able to buy any lives
if they produced only two."
This thought struck me,
and I felt very anxious at that moment.
After hearing from everyone,
Team White doesn't want to go to war...
until the very end.
The members of Team Blue
are busy protecting themselves.
The members of Team Red...
were really tight with each other.
If one of them is about to die,
I wished to make them think,
"Won't it be more efficient to start a war
to take their lives?"
I've set everything up.
- The maximum is two lives.
- Right.
- Two lives for ten credits.
- Two lives?
- Isn't it better to make them get none...
if we are to get one life?
They must be short on credits...
for them to be desperate.
Is that what you think?
We should go for 1 or 2.
Let's decide after hearing about
how many they want.
"Do you need any credits?"
If they say they don't need any,
- should we make no trades today?
- Right.
Let's ask them how many they want.
Where should we talk? Here?
Isn't it too open here?
- We can talk quietly.
- Right.
- Were you able to produce...
- Us?
- a lot today?
- We produced quite a lot.
This team looks competent.
What's good about credits is that...
they don't seem to be...
that valuable to this community.
- They aren't as valuable right now.
- Right.
Everyone wants to avoid death.
Everything is centered around lives...
- at this moment.
- Right.
Do you have a good amount of lives?
No. To be honest,
we weren't able to produce a lot today.
We were awful.
Why? You should've used
a lot of your credits.
- We were careful with our credits.
- Right.
We had to spend 2 to 3 credits...
- to earn one life.
- I see.
Nothing has changed from yesterday.
- As for today...
- You must...
produce a lot of lives.
Right. You must produce a lot...
- to maintain this peace.
- Right.
- The moment you fail to do so,
- Lives are crucial right now.
it will be the start of a war.
If we are to avoid going to war...
and live as a community,
we need to make sacrifices
with each other...
or reach an agreement.
If that's not the case,
we will work for ourselves...
and end up going to war.
To be honest, we aren't sure...
which direction to take.
- I see.
- Right.
Not at all.
- Why are they fighting so much?
- They must be going to war.
Gosh.
It feels like they're about to go to war.
- It's like it's going to happen now.
- Right.
I did my best...
to stop them from going to war.
I thought about this.
I think my role is Switzerland.
- A neutral country.
- A neutral country?
That is why I'm excluded from
going to war.
Right. That would be too much
of a disadvantage for you.
I am to be a trader while maintaining
friendly relationships with everyone.
That's by selling things.
My mission is to...
get items handed over to me...
and to earn my prize money
by selling them.
Black is...
my only smoking buddy,
but I can't trust him at all.
When someone looks determined and smart,
they have a greater goal.
There's a big chance
that he's hiding something.
When I went on a different survival show,
I got duped by everyone who looked nice.
I got duped so many times.
I was an expert at getting duped.
While playing a fool,
I am determined to...
go after my target.
Paul seems to trust Black.
Black will try to dupe Paul,
but Paul will dupe him instead.
Black is on his own.
He has a very vague role.
He seems to be an almighty being,
but he's also someone who can't do much.
He had such a neutral role.
I kept my guard up...
as he could get us from behind
at any moment.
I have a question.
It's quite obvious that the team
to be with Team White will win.
- It'll be 9 against 3.
- Right.
It'll be one or the other.
Which side will you favor more?
We will seek peace.
- Peace is our priority.
- Your mind is set?
No alliances?
- It's because...
- That will be inevitable, but...
No one will ever try to fight
against nine.
There's a big chance...
that the 3 who go against 9
will get destroyed.
I believe it's important for us...
to maintain friendly relationships.
- We want to keep things peaceful.
- Right.
As for Team White,
the value of diamonds went up by a lot...
after the announcement of war.
Even without my help,
they were making good deals.
I thought hard about how to make them
go to war.
If I want a war to start,
I should make the fee for war
very affordable.
I should make them think,
"Should we go to war?"
Once the members of Team White
start getting wiped out,
a more balanced war will be available.
I believe I can...
aim after Team White when that happens.
To maintain peace,
we must each make some sacrifices.
- But...
- It would be better...
to give out more credits.
We must provide more...
- for Team Blue to produce more.
- Right.
This is what I'm curious about.
Are you able to sell lives at this point?
As of right now,
we aren't short on credits.
Do you not need...
any credits right now?
That's not it!
- That sounded so cold.
- No.
- That's not true.
- I was told that credits weren't needed.
- That's not it.
- This is what it's like.
It's not that credits aren't needed.
- We...
- We really want them,
- We want them...
- but here's nothing we can do.
Since you can't offer anything,
- so you can't ask for anything?
- Yes.
- Exactly.
- We'd appreciate it...
if you gave us some, but it's not like...
we have no shame.
True.
Even from my perspective,
credits may not be
that useful at the moment.
But when making necessary trades...
and doing productive activities,
credits are a must.
Underestimate credits,
and we might all go down together.
Honestly, all the teams are in the green.
Let's see how much we produce tomorrow...
- and talk again.
- But to produce enough tomorrow,
- don't you need credits right now?
- True.
- Like, as a bit of backup.
- It'd be nice if we did.
To be frank, we were very prudent...
about using credits today...
- as we didn't have many.
- I thought so.
Credits are useful.
Our team used a handful of them today.
We also produced a lot.
But here's the thing.
Even if we were to use credits,
- we'd need basic knowledge.
- True.
It's hard to grasp without it.
Don't say it. It's making me feel small.
- But...
- I know.
We got several questions from hints.
The best is...
Thirty minutes left of trading.
I'm feeling very anxious.
I'll go give them a heads-up about...
- the trade with us.
- Okay.
- If so...
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
- I won't join your conversation.
Our teams need to trade,
- but the remaining time...
- Right.
We also need to make a trade
with every team,
- so we'll rush it.
- We'll be there in a bit.
- We'll be there in five minutes.
- Okay.
Will it be impossible to solve
even 1 or 2 questions?
We'll be in a worse deficit
than yesterday.
- Then...
- What do we do?
- We...
- Can we make free exchanges?
- Exchanges?
- If you don't use the credits now,
- you can't use them...
- They must have...
- tomorrow either, right?
- enough for tomorrow.
- But you see,
- Yes?
- Team Blue should get some credits.
- You want to give them some?
If we could get even just one life,
I wanted to use credits
to set sail tomorrow.
Waiting for another day isn't that bad.
But that just feels like wasting a day.
- Give us time to think about it,
- If things get worse...
so if you were to give us
an offer first...
- Say that we overdo ourselves.
- Okay.
We overdo ourselves
and distribute something.
How many credits are you willing to trade?
Eight.
- Eight?
- Yes.
Sorry?
(Maillard's offer)
Eight credits for one life.
Is that telling them to go all-in
and earn lives tomorrow?
Isn't it a little too unfair?
It's way too good for us.
- The thing is...
- Why worry about that?
- Honestly, right now, we're almost...
- It's not a 1-on-1 trade.
- It's just...
- This is for the whole economy.
- It's practically...
- Think of it as preventing war.
- Exactly.
- Were we that bad today?
- I...
- Without any lives,
- all of us are in grave trouble.
- I seriously want to crawl under a rock.
- But listen. If we were able to get...
- Yes?
- resources in advance and did so.
- Okay.
- We saw the hint.
But if we fail to answer anything...
We need to cross the line.
That'll improve our chances,
- and I mean our overall chances.
- The chances increase.
- Let's grow the market.
- Then...
- First...
- Whether we don't get the answer...
because we have no credits
or even with credits,
the result is the same
if we don't get the answer tomorrow.
- The deal...
- We need to cross the line.
- Whether we make a deal or not,
- What now?
we're out of time.
- For now, let's get moving.
- Okay.
Regardless of whether we do it or not,
- we will bring it over.
- We'll bring ours too.
- No, let's meet there.
- Right.
- We'll meet you there.
- Okay, we'll meet you there.
- Right.
- We'll bring ours too.
- We'd better hurry.
- Right.
Do we have enough to spare, like one?
Trading 1 life for 8 credits is
a very generous offer.
True, I agree.
I didn't expect them to be that generous.
- They...
- But they realized it too that...
- Right.
- yesterday's deal was a total jackpot.
Either way, their goal seems to be
to find the exact value...
and increase the resources,
not to chip away at us...
or be all calculative about losses.
Producing lives is extremely important...
- right now.
- They're being smart.
When we do something,
like using the hint,
- we barely have any credits.
- True.
Do we agree to the offer?
- Yes.
- Even if we negotiate?
- It's such a generous offer,
which I really think we should accept.
- All we can offer is five.
- Yes?
The other team gets five,
- and so do we?
- Correct.
Your deal with the other team
didn't cancel, right?
The deal hasn't been set in stone yet.
Honestly, they had nothing to offer.
But we...
If they're not in,
we don't have a deal with Team Blue today.
If your deal with Team Blue falls through,
is there a way
we could get those credits instead?
The thing is, if the deal with
Team Blue falls apart,
it'll be bad for all of us.
Only when we give some help to
Team Blue with...
- some credits...
- It's our way of supporting them.
We have to raise Team Blue together.
- That's what we also want.
- Great.
- But if it doesn't go as planned,
- If it doesn't go as planned...
- we might want more credits.
- Got it.
- We'll even cheer you on from the side.
- Okay.
- I'll go bring our credits.
- Okay, go ahead.
There has to be something.
- Are you in on it?
- We are.
Got it.
Don't tell the quantity to the other team.
- Got it.
- Of course not.
Run.
I know how hard that is,
so I can't let the offer go.
Running up those stairs is not easy.
It's tough.
(A fierce determination
to raise Team Blue)
(Out of the 29,)
(Maillard takes 13 with him.)
The time...
- The time is...
- Well...
- Everyone, the time is...
- It won't take long.
Do you mind if we quickly trade first?
- Go ahead.
- Sure.
- We'll be back fast.
- Be careful.
Peacefully, you know?
Let's be quick, okay?
(Maillard's offer)
Who will be paying the credits
to make this trade?
We came in without discussing that.
- Our team will pay for it for now.
- Okay, got it.
The trade has been completed.
Please collect the resources and exit.
(1 life)
One, two, three, four...
(Traded with 7 credits)
- Thank you.
- I've collected them.
- Please produce a lot tomorrow.
- Okay.
- We'll be rooting for you.
- I'll study before going to bed tonight.
For your information, the disease book...
- Yes?
- was used today.
- Is the hint really...
- It's in there.
- in the book?
- The answer is in there.
The thing is, our books differ.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Anyway, we used the disease book.
I'd better look at the books thoroughly.
(Teams White and Red trade next.)
So you used the disease book.
It would be nice...
if we shared the themes...
- of our books.
- Right?
The Trading Station has been activated.
(10 diamonds)
Four.
(4 credits)
- Four and ten. Correct?
- Yes.
All done.
We're checking the submitted amount.
Please wait a moment.
Does Team White also appoint the leader
every morning?
- Yes, we did this morning.
- You did?
Yes.
How's it being the leader?
I thought there'd be a benefit,
like a life I could use alone.
- Right?
- But there's nothing.
Maybe it helps improve our stamina.
But there's this one perk.
Before going to bed,
if I were to just lose it,
- Kill everyone out of the blue?
- kill everyone besides myself.
What if you lose it for real?
It's kind of like
socially killing yourself.
The trade has been completed.
Please collect the resources and exit.
(Teams White and Red are done trading.)
- Good work.
- Someone's carrying money...
in their pocket.
- It's just that...
- Each is worth 1,000 dollars.
- It's easy to carry around.
- Don't lose it, okay?
It's priceless.
- They didn't take long.
- Good work.
- We made it in time.
- Peace has come to everyone.
- We got through the day.
- Nice.
- Good work.
How the game unfolded today was
somewhat satisfactory.
Team Blue kept the alliance of 9-to-3.
What was promised was 2,
but they gave us 3.
"When something happens,
we have to be together."
We gave each other such trust.
Of course, I still have my guard up,
but as long as
it's in their best interest, I trust them.
It's hard to believe that...
they only produced two lives today.
We put it strongly today.
"Use your hints and such
to produce as many lives as possible,"
"so that we can find a way
for all of us to survive tomorrow."
I'm hoping that
they'll get the answers right.
I believe we're being too conservative,
which is frustrating.
We currently have many lives in storage.
It could leave them feeling
a sense of loss.
Until today, they kept saying,
"You must survive."
"You're indispensable."
But behind our backs,
they would definitely be like,
"You can live another 2 to 3 days."
"You totally can, but you're not willing
to trade them?"
When such a feeling of loss emerges,
war can break out.
"As the leader,
I can just dogmatically hurt them."
When such thoughts crossed my mind
every now and then,
I couldn't make that choice in the end.
Why is being a leader so tough?
I want to quit being one already.
Mining the resources is
much harder than expected.
Even so,
the market is filled with lives now.
It worries me. Only when...
there aren't enough lives
will people feel the pinch...
and start a war.
"It won't be easy until Day Two."
That was what I thought.
"Suddenly starting a war on Day Two
isn't easy."
"If the productive activity is tough,"
"Day Three might be hopeful,"
was what I thought.
We have to mine at least two lives
to survive until the day after tomorrow.
At this rate,
because of the two that Team Blue earned,
- we're all stalled.
- Exactly.
Our economy has stagnated.
It's not flowing.
Will everyone survive today?
Here's the only elimination scenario.
- The leader's betrayal.
- Exactly.
That's the only case.
But will these two betray the others?
I think Luna should make up her mind.
- By getting rid of three people,
- That?
she could last quite a while.
Her chances double.
Right? It's four days' worth.
- What's more...
- Four days' worth in one go.
There's a limited amount of supply,
so that could be
how we can survive together.
Should I ask her quietly today?
For everyone's eternal life,
get rid of some people.
We could help eliminate
the members of Team White.
Internal conflict will arise.
We do have
an overwhelming number of diamonds.
We'd better be careful
because if we say we barely have any,
we'd be deceiving.
Should we eat today?
Because it feels like
there's no money circulating.
Should we release a few...
by buying food?
But...
if we give it to Team Black,
it's not going to circulate anyway.
He's taking them to himself.
- But it looks like...
- So there's no point of spending any.
they're all thinking about something good
for the public.
It's not for the public.
They're begging those with lives
to survive.
We have no reason to give them diamonds...
when we're already eating our lives away.
Unless we're going there...
to eat fried chicken and pork belly...
- like crazy,
- So...
we're paying only one diamond...
for one bagel. That's about it.
So what's the point?
There still is a point.
- There is a point.
- There is a point, but...
- I get what you mean.
- If that's the reason,
we've talked about pizza, eggs,
and soya milk already.
If we say we bought food,
they'd think we only spent a few.
So if we end up spending 2 or 3 more
to show them,
they'll think, "They must've spent 5.
They must've spent 7."
It makes no difference.
To be honest,
I don't want to spend diamonds on food.
Okay. We agreed...
to respect each other.
It's dinner time.
Please have dinner in the Town Hall.
(The Town Hall is still empty.)
Even for him.
I thought it was dinner time.
We already chose what to eat.
We can just microwave it, right?
(Team Blue saved pizza during lunch.)
How long do we microwave it?
Eight to nine minutes.
He's here.
Where is everyone?
I think they're coming.
If no one's here yet,
should we give it to him now?
- Sounds good.
- Yes.
(They hid 1 life...)
Will it fit in here?
(in the glass case
for black-market deals.)
- You should...
- Take it...
- when there's no one.
- And...
It's the payment for the pizza.
Okay.
You already opened it.
On credit.
(Although it's given to Team Black,)
(the amount of resources doesn't change.)
Can you...
tell us...
- just in case...
- Things you took?
- Yes.
- Say you paid 2 for 1 egg and that.
Three eggs and one pizza.
- One pizza?
- Yes.
But they wouldn't ask.
It's a secret.
- Hello.
- You're very early.
- Yes. We were hungry.
- I can see that.
What do you want to eat?
What do you want? The lunchbox?
How much is the fried chicken?
I need at least two for that.
It's chicken.
The fried chicken deserves two.
- How about we have one?
- You'll have one?
- Half and half?
- Half and half, please.
Okay.
Everyone.
There are only two fried chickens left.
- There are only two fried chickens left.
- That's his gimmick.
That's his gimmick.
Oh, thank you.
- Nice.
- For the fried chicken.
It's worth 2,000 dollars.
- It's worth 2,000 dollars.
- A chicken worth 2,000 dollars.
We traded a life for food.
Yet, she wants to give him diamonds.
I don't see the point.
The idea of surviving together.
How others see us
and what they think of us.
She cares about that so much.
I kept thinking, "That isn't the point."
Let me have the meat dumplings.
I'll have an egg and soya milk.
- It's healthy.
- Very healthy.
- It's all protein.
- Yes.
Today, I'll make it a combo...
and give you a fried chicken for five.
Five for all this and a fried chicken?
- Really?
- We can always order more later.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Do you want to have ramyeon and dumplings?
Sure.
(Team Red picks up the food they had.)
Let's go.
Is Team Red not eating?
Is Team Red preparing for a war?
We're late.
Sorry.
Oh, they don't need to buy anything
for dinner.
What?
- They're rich.
- We bought it earlier.
I have to sell ramyeon,
but they brought ramyeon.
- Come on.
- No more ramyeon sales today.
I'm doomed. I'm so bad at sales.
When did you order the fried chicken?
About 15 to 20 minutes? Maybe?
I have a feeling you can guess the time.
- No.
- Are you an athlete?
- What did you do?
- Kind of. I was a soldier.
- A soldier?
- Now,
I'm in the bomb disposal unit.
That's scary.
I'm so proud of you.
Even though that's not what I do,
- It's reassuring.
- we're on the same team.
What do you want me to do?
Leia, may I ask you
what you do for a living?
- Me?
- At first, I got a feeling...
that you were a journalist.
You have a very good deduction.
The occupation...
- It doesn't matter.
- doesn't really matter.
If it did, it'd be unfair for me.
- Right.
The special meal has arrived.
- Oh, chicken.
- Ta-da.
That's intense.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
I feel rich to have chicken here.
Right.
Hey.
The 3 of us had 2 meals...
for five diamonds.
That's 5,000 dollars,
and that's very expensive.
We decided to tighten our belts...
and find a way through.
That's what was on my mind.
It didn't make sense to me.
We're not here to have
chicken or pork belly.
We're not here to waste our money here.
We plan to secure
as much prize money as possible.
And we'll spend it...
on our play instead of food.
I don't think we'll be having
any luxurious meals until the end.
That scares me.
May I have your attention, please?
We will now play the Majority Rules Game.
The Majority Rules Game will be played
no more than six times.
Using the questions on values
from the pre-test,
the residents will speak...
their opinions freely.
Any resident who volunteers to speak...
gets a banana as a prize.
After everyone finishes speaking,
residents will vote for
the approach that is likely...
to win more people's support.
After voting,
the person who successfully voted
for the one most people agreed with...
and matches majority's code...
gets two points.
The person who successfully voted
for the one most people agreed with,
but doesn't match majority's code...
gets one point.
The pre-test had various questions.
Some questions might have...
a different code
from the way you answered.
Regardless of the response,
the points are calculated...
based on the final code.
Therefore, if more people are...
expected to vote against your code,
you may vote for a different opinion...
or make a different statement...
to win points.
It's important to stir people...
for points, right?
You're right.
It's a matter of exposing my code...
to get more points...
or use a feint to protect my code,
but get a few points.
Also, a resident
with the most outstanding statement...
will become an MVP in every game.
(An MVP will be selected
through voting at the end of every game.)
The MVP will...
receive extra three points...
regardless of majority's opinion.
However, if two people receive
the same number of votes,
no MVP will be announced.
(They played the Majority Rules Game
in the evening of Day 1.)
(Self-driving cars should be designed
to save majority...)
(and sacrifice the driver
in case of a crash.)
It's important to follow the rule.
The moment you drive a self-driving car,
you're up alone against many,
so you'll die.
Would you drive it then?
Will self-driving car companies be able to
sell them?
Everyone. Driving on your own is
the whole point of driving.
Don't drive a self-driving car.
Still, it's better to save many...
than just one.
If a sacrifice is necessary,
wouldn't it be better to sacrifice myself
than sacrificing many?
A sacrifice is wonderful,
but it's unreasonable...
to force you to sacrifice yourself...
the moment you get in the car.
I don't think it's unfair.
Why is there no option?
Just drive another car.
You don't buy a self-driving car
to sacrifice yourself.
You buy it to make driving easy.
But if that condition is given,
it's not like you have no other options
for cars.
According to the self-driving car data,
the chance of an accident is...
significantly lower...
when AI drives
than when the driver drives the car.
For a motor company,
the accident handling cost is lower
when a few people die.
In terms of the cost...
That's crazy.
Think about it.
Make up your mind,
so we can share the points together.
Let's do this.
There's no time.
Let me make a quick statement.
(Majority Rules Game)
Hurry up.
No.
(It was so intense, they ran out of time
on Day 1.)
To prevent any accidents...
- caused by lack of driving skills...
- Time's up.
That's a shame.
Six for principlism
and seven for consequentialism.
It's 6 to 7.
That was so close.
That's one vote difference.
I supported principlism,
but I needed the point.
So I shifted to consequentialism.
I knew I'd still win a point.
I thought the majority would...
support consequentialism.
But I just didn't want to support it.
That was just wrong.
Even if that was the majority's opinion,
I just couldn't agree.
Today's MVP is Vector.
(Vector wins 3 extra points
for becoming an MVP.)
Vector did make a good point,
and it'd be advantageous...
to make Vector an MVP...
since he doesn't belong to any team.
We don't know
what these points are for yet.
- Right.
Anyway, it's going to be important...
as it goes. That's all we need to know.
There's nothing bad
about having many points.
The topic
for the Majority Rules Game is...
giving everyone a chance
to take the test...
creates a fair competition.
- Ability and structure?
- Fair competition.
- Oh, is that right?
- Ability and structure?
Structure and ability.
A fair competition?
What is "fairness?"
They'll keep increasing the level
to more uncomfortable topics.
Things are definitely more sensitive
than yesterday.
For an hour starting now,
residents can freely share
their opinions...
on the podium set up in front.
I don't know what to say.
Which way do we go?
Which way...
I'm Team Ability.
Are you Team Ability?
Yes.
Are you Team Ability or Team Structure?
I'm not sure. I'm thinking about it.
For today's Majority Rules Game,
should I lie about my values?
I spoke up so much yesterday,
so I thought it'd be very easy
for people to guess my code...
if I ended up revealing another one.
Because this is related
to our personal scores,
I thought higher scores would be
more convenient than lower scores.
So I realized that the strategy...
of totally hiding my code...
will make it difficult for me...
to earn personal points.
I felt this needed more thought
than expected.
"An equal opportunity to take the test..."
This is so hard.
I'll go.
(The first speaker
of the Majority Rules Game, Luna)
Normally, I would've been able...
to present more arguments
for the other side.
But since I was on the "Ability" side,
I thought I needed to push that more.
That's why I quickly thought
of my arguments.
Firstly, I believe that giving everyone
an equal opportunity to take the test...
is enough to satisfy
the conditions of fair competition.
Of course,
there are other necessary conditions.
For example, some people may not be
able to afford test preparation books.
Some people may not be
able to get good private education.
I can think of those conditions.
But because it's not possible
to add those conditions,
I think it's enough.
Let's say we add extra conditions.
That will cause
other points of unfairness.
In the end, we cannot create
what we call "fairness."
There will just be
new points of unfairness.
What I believe "enough" means here...
is letting people start...
at a reasonably similar starting line
within realistic conditions.
That's why I believe we can say
it's enough...
to give people the opportunity
to take the same test.
Thank you.
(Luna argued for "Ability"
in accordance with her code.)
I was planning to speak a bit later,
but I came to argue for the other side.
I go to schools...
to speak about sex education.
When you teach sex education in schools,
you run into very interesting situations.
There was an elderly person
at my lesson...
sitting next to a teenager.
I thought, "What's going on here?"
They were the child of immigrants.
That's quite common.
Children of immigrants...
aren't totally familiar with our language.
Us saying to those people,
"Hey, you are the one who chose Korea."
"Then you should put in the effort
and do the same as everyone else."
I believe that is too cruel...
and dismissive of those policies.
I actually studied abroad in the US.
Some could say I had a big disadvantage...
compared to local students
when I took the SATs.
Was I able to ask for more time...
because English wasn't my mother tongue?
Not at all.
If those who are taking...
the CSAT or SAT have the same goals,
I believe it's only fair
to take the test...
under the same conditions.
Does this need to be on the stand?
I can hold it, right?
So cool.
Vector, who spoke just now,
had a disadvantage,
but won with his ability.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- I really admire you.
But on the other hand, I think about this.
Do you think the results...
we get are fair just because
we had the same opportunities?
Don't you think
that's a bit of an illusion?
Here's an example.
A company is picking ten people
with an aptitude test,
and the top ten highest scorers
turn out to be all women.
In those situations, HR teams sometimes...
add a male candidate
who had a lower score.
I gave an example with one gender,
but the opposite happens as well.
When there are too many people...
of one category
when putting together a team,
companies take reactive measures
to compensate for it.
So I believe we need to let go...
of this fantasy we have about "fairness."
Also, thinking about the story
in this way...
will make it extra irritating.
Try putting yourself in that situation.
Imagine you're in that situation,
and someone else got in
because they got extra points.
That makes us feel
like something has been taken from us.
That makes it feel off-putting.
But you could create policies in this way.
Make the pie bigger.
From that perspective,
I believe we could at least improve...
those policies in a way that benefits...
the greater good of society.
I developed a crush.
She just speaks so well.
She criticized
what the previous speakers said...
while building her argument.
I really like people
who can speak like that.
Out of the words written here,
I believe the word "fair..."
and the word "competition..."
don't really go well together.
Because when we get stuck
in the trap of wondering,
"What is the range of fairness
we need to consider..."
"for most people to think
something is fair,"
we end up thinking about it endlessly.
For example,
let's think about a track race.
If we can only say a race is fair...
if all runners have
the perfectly same physique,
the same leg length, for example,
the same amount of training,
the same condition on race day,
the same exact shoes,
and so on and so forth,
it'll feel too difficult
to meet those conditions at all.
That's why we aim for conditions
that can realistically be met.
By allowing everyone to take
the same test in the same amount of time,
we aim to at least make
the starting line the same for everyone.
It specifically says here, "enough."
(It's not enough, Structure, 2,
It's enough, Ability, 3)
I don't think "enough..."
and "at least" mean the same thing.
I think I would've agreed if this said,
"It satisfies the 'minimum' conditions."
I want to think a bit
about what sort of behavior...
the words "at least" and "enough..."
draw out of people.
When we believe something is enough,
we no longer act.
Something surprised me while being here.
Once my survival was guaranteed,
I can feel my body tighten up.
I become afraid to move.
I want you all to think
about how the word "enough..."
doesn't call us to action.
The meaning of the word "competition..."
is to rank people.
Even today, some of us will earn points,
and some of us won't.
I believe the results of competitions...
are inherently unfair.
The competition for a banana
is so intense.
"Enough," "overwhelmingly," "absolutely."
These sorts of sentences
are likely to be incorrect.
I was a bit surprised
that half of the people...
were arguing for "Ability,"
which is the opposite of that.
"Really? Are you sure?"
I'm still a bit surprised.
I guess that's how people think.
Listening to people
with different opinions than me...
is so fun.
Despite these differing opinions,
we're living together well in one land.
My daughter gifted me a poem,
and I particularly liked this one line.
"What roots does this tree have,"
"what trunk does this tree have,"
"that it was able to protect my yard
against these rough rainstorms?"
That was the line.
The roots of my parents,
as in, the environment they grew up in.
And the trunk, as in,
the efforts that they made.
"How did they become such good parents?"
That's the meaning the poem had for me.
For some trees,
the seeds fall on very good land.
Then they can really grow out their roots.
If so, they will be able to grow
strong trunks as well.
But some seeds fall in the desert.
If so, that person can work very hard...
but only grow thorns.
So I'm saying environment is important.
We all live together on one land.
Isn't it important for us to hold
that land together with our roots?
We need to prevent a landslide.
(It's not enough, Structure, 4,
It's enough, Ability, 4)
I had this thought.
He moved it out of the way.
Subsidies are nice.
Welfare is nice.
But I think sometimes,
that help takes away...
from one's will to take on a challenge.
I'll give you an example.
Let's say a rapper...
had a tough upbringing.
"I came from the ghetto."
"I got myself here
working at a pizza joint."
"I was mopping floors."
"Now, I'm wearing a Rolex."
"Do you see that? I did that."
But let's say the government
gives him a bunch of handouts...
to make things fair for him.
"I came here with disaster relief funds."
Doesn't that sound pretty uncool?
But won't you accept those funds?
I will. I appreciate them.
I want there to be more. But...
- I'm just presenting another side.
- Okay.
(He's so funny.)
Donkey was really shouting up there.
He was like an angry donkey on stage.
(Donkey, Stand-up comedian)
I thought I wanted to make
some sort of an impact,
even if that was by being ridiculous
and making people laugh.
We need fair opportunities,
not just for humanitarian reasons,
like to help a disadvantaged child...
make a better life for themselves,
but also to make our society wealthier.
I believe the total wealth
of our society increases...
when a person with a good brain
is in a good position.
Let's say one person is born
into a rich family...
but isn't super smart,
and one person is very poor
but very smart.
If you ask which of these two
have the higher probability...
of getting into Seoul National University
in Korea's current society,
the person living in Gangnam...
is slightly more likely
to get into Seoul University.
Why? Because the opportunities
to study are already uneven.
And let's think,
"Who are the people taking tests?"
Most test takers are minors...
or people in their early 20s.
The life of a minor is shaped more...
by what is given to them
than by their own will.
Some kids get lucky with rich parents.
Or some kids won't be so lucky and end up
with parents who aren't as rich.
A society with disparities
in educational opportunities...
shouldn't be considered a fair society.
That's my opinion.
Some of you pointed out that...
smart people would more likely be accepted
into Seoul National University.
But being smart isn't everything.
Well, they might be more interested
in arts or sports.
Or they just might have poor character.
Then there's a high probability
of not getting into SNU.
I think those were limited examples.
You said that children
from wealthy backgrounds...
would have a higher likelihood...
of getting into Seoul National University.
I think
that's a huge generalization error.
I'd like to use my experience
when I was studying abroad as an example.
I met so many students who grew up
in much more supportive homes...
and had far better
educational opportunities.
I worked really hard to beat them.
In the end,
I got into a more prestigious university.
Now that my annual income is higher
than theirs...
and I'm earning more than them,
the feeling of accomplishment
is far greater than theirs.
Political correctness is widespread
in the US.
Sometimes, schools give extra points
to Black students.
So if two students had identical grades,
a Black applicant might get accepted
while a White applicant wouldn't.
If you think about it,
this student was discriminated...
based on the color of their skin.
Structural interventions...
might just end up causing conflicts
within the society.
Well, she mentioned the racial issue.
Bringing up racial discrimination
or reverse discrimination was iffy.
All the speakers here
are neither Black nor White.
Is it something we can bring up
on behalf of other people?
I was a bit concerned.
People are concerned
about these structural changes...
such as reverse discrimination.
If the changes are too much,
people will criticize them
and they will eventually disappear.
The market economy...
isn't the only place
the Invisible Hand exists.
I believe we naturally find the balance...
in social agreements.
With that said,
I don't think that argument fits here.
(The speaking time is over.)
The speaking time has ended.
You will now vote
for the Majority Rules Game.
Residents, vote for the side
you believe will be the majority.
Write down your pick for MVP.
- And drop it in the ballot box.
- My gosh.
This is tough.
Once all votes are in,
today's majority side and MVP
will be revealed.
Why didn't you speak today, Boss?
- Me?
- I was curious about your opinion.
- I agree with the statement.
- Okay.
But my experience
is mostly military-related.
So it might be uncomfortable.
I might have found it uncomfortable
discussing it.
So let me use the physical fitness
as an example.
When female soldiers
have to do 50 repetitions,
male soldiers have to do 80 repetitions.
Some said that it wasn't fair.
"Bullets don't steer clear of someone
just because they are women."
I've heard a lot of people say that.
But I think it's fair...
because men and women differ
in physical strength...
and muscular power.
But I thought I would be uncomfortable
discussing that.
- So you were being careful.
- So I decided not to speak up.
Today, our debate was neck and neck.
Everyone came up to speak today.
Yes, totally.
Wasn't it really interesting?
- You got those crazy eyes.
- Why are you so excited?
She loves a dopamine rush.
She can't say no to it.
The results of the Majority Rules Game...
- will be announced now.
- Drumroll, please.
- Today's theme was...
"Giving everyone an equal opportunity
to take the test..."
"is enough to satisfy the conditions
of fair competition."
- Here are the results.
- Let's see.
I'm nervous.
Three votes for Structure.
Ten votes for Ability.
Today's majority side
has leaned toward Ability.
- No way.
- Ten to three?
- They all switched.
- No way.
- They switched.
People who leaned
toward Structure initially...
- That's interesting.
- I'm sorry.
- That's right.
- Here's an honest statement.
- Did you vote for Ability?
- Yes.
- I was desperate.
- Really?
I still don't agree
with ability-based policies.
I lean heavily toward Structure.
I still believe structure and policies
play a crucial role in our society.
But this is the Majority Rules Game.
After listening to everyone,
I counted the votes.
It seemed they were the majority,
so I voted for that.
I noticed something about the residents
arguing for Ability.
It looked like
they weren't going to change their vote.
I thought people
who leaned toward Structure...
might change their vote.
Deep down, I still lean toward Structure.
But I voted for Ability
and got on the majority side.
First of all,
even if it didn't agree with my belief,
I was going to side with the majority
no matter what.
(Structure: Leia, Salt, Hamlet)
(Ability: Luna, Paul, Maillard, Donkey,
Vector, Boss, Genie, Siseon, Izaha, Pitou)
- I thought I wouldn't change my vote.
- This is crazy.
- Points were at stake.
- Of course.
- You can't help it.
- I changed toward the end.
Leia and Izaha received the most votes
for today's MVP.
- As it's a tie,
- Two people?
- no one is MVP.
- It's invalid.
(There's no MVP today
because the vote ended in a tie.)
- The vote is void.
- What? No!
- My goodness.
- What?
- What? It's a tie?
- No.
- That's not good.
- Really?
It's not good.
That's zero points.
Today, I voted for Leia.
But the vote ended in a tie.
The vote was void.
So I thought, "Had I not voted for Leia,"
"Izaha would've gotten it."
I voted for Izaha.
Of course, I vote for the resident
who gets close to convincing me.
But I also vote for the resident
who does well in the debate.
Should I say he had a nice flow?
So I voted for him as the MVP.
To be honest, I wanted to be the MVP...
because once you're chosen as the MVP,
you get three points.
I didn't even vote for myself
when I ran for class president...
in elementary school.
(Leia, Journalist)
I voted for myself for the first time.
I didn't expect much.
But they paid attention to what I said
and could relate to it.
So I was grateful and had fun.
- Great job, everyone.
- But...
- Can't they both get three points?
- Great job.
- Congratulations.
- Well done.
What a bummer.
- My gosh.
- This is tough.
They should both get three points.
(MVP: Void)
The leaders will have a negotiation
in 30 minutes.
- A negotiation?
- When the negotiation time is called,
leaders of each team...
- must gather in the Community Center.
- What?
- Leaders will have a negotiation?
I guess the three leaders...
- will talk.
- I guess something's up.
- Something's up.
- They didn't do this last night.
- Right. I guess so.
- Let's hurry up and go back.
- Okay. Let's go.
Let's hurry.
- Thirty minutes.
- What can the leaders discuss?
- Exactly.
- The negotiation...
I bet it has to do with a policy.
- They said they'd reveal it shortly.
- Yes.
I'll brief you guys once I come back.
Okay.
Hold on. What do you think...
we'll discuss?
I should take my notebook, right?
- Yes. Take notes on everything.
- Yes. You should.
- And share them with us.
- Yes. Right.
I don't know
what exactly we'll be discussing.
Right, we don't know.
- This is such an important assignment.
- Right. Even if...
We have no idea what it is.
(On the other hand, Vector is at ease
since it's just him in the team.)
Leaders will have a negotiation soon.
The negotiation will be held every day
starting today.
The decisions made
during this negotiation...
can affect each team's resources
and conditions.
- It could affect the resources.
- I see.
- It could affect our team?
- I wonder what it is.
Once the negotiation ends,
today's life submission
will take place next.
- Take the lives with you.
- I see.
I totally forgot about that.
Leaders, bring the lives
you will submit today...
and resources you may use
during the negotiation...
- Resources...
- to the Community Center.
- Resources to use during the negotiation?
- What does that mean?
- You should take some credits with you.
- What? We have to use more of them?
- What? My gosh.
I don't want to use our credits.
I'll just bring the entire box.
- Okay.
- Yes.
It might be better
to keep them in the dark about...
- how many lives we have.
- Yes.
- We must trust you. That's the only way.
- Right.
- We have to give her the key.
- We trust you.
- Don't worry. And crush them.
- I got this. I'll be back.
- Good luck.
- As for this moment,
pursue Practicality.
- I always do.
- She always pursues Practicality.
- Then pursue it even more.
- Yes.
They're our lives.
You can't negotiate with them.
Of course, I won't.
- Of course, I won't.
- You'll have to come back then.
Of course, I won't.
These are our precious lives.
We went through so much trouble
to earn these lives.
- To the Community Center?
- Yes.
- Did you pack them?
- Yes, I did.
He packed enough.
I can't just take one.
- What? You only packed one life?
- My gosh.
What are you doing?
We're watching you.
Don't be silly.
- How...
- You're flustered.
You're trying to send us home
with that nice smile.
- My gosh.
- So you can be here for a week.
- Gosh, that's funny.
- What are you talking about?
Are you leaving now?
- Yes. They called the leaders now.
- They told me to come now.
- Okay. See you.
- Good luck.
You're waiting out here.
They told us to bring our resources.
Right.
They said we'd need them to negotiate.
You're going to join us?
- Yes. He's also a leader.
- I'm a leader too.
I'm a leader too.
(The isolation
of a one-person team leader)
- I'm a leader too.
- You're okay, right?
I had to use the bathroom. Sorry I'm late.
- Let's go in.
- Okay.
Why did they ask us
to bring our resources?
Leaders,
stand at your designated spot.
I think we have to stand over the light.
- This is black, right?
- Right there.
That's black.
- It's a black light.
- Yes.
(Leader Negotiation)
Welcome...
to the Leader Negotiation.
Today's Leader Negotiation will begin now.
At the first Leader Negotiation,
I was like, "What's this?"
The announcement said
we had to bring our resources.
I wondered if we would be able
to help each other...
or trade with other leaders.
During trading, we assumed that...
we could only trade
using our assigned resources.
But I thought we'd be able to trade
with other resources.
I thought it would be fun.
Perhaps, I can anticipate a twist.
Or it might change their opinions a bit.
I was super nervous
and didn't know what to do...
when I attended the negotiation.
"Leaders must fulfill
their convictions..."
"while bearing the responsibility
if things go wrong."
I've always thought
that was the requirement of a true leader.
To expand more on this idea,
I want leaders to contribute
to the community.
I'm hoping
the other leaders have a similar view.
First, the current pollution index
for the entire Community Town...
will be revealed.
The current pollution index...
- is at 15.
- Pollution?
Once the pollution index reaches 100,
the Community enters
a state of saturation.
Please pay attention to the index.
- The pollution index is at 15.
- The next item on the agenda...
will be announced shortly.
The pollution index?
The pollution index.
It's finally revealed. That's good.
There was an announcement
about the pollution index.
I was relieved.
Without that announcement,
it would've been very difficult for us...
to bring up pollution-free credits.
Yes. As you can see,
- it's marked in red.
- Yes.
I should give you an explanation.
- I see.
- The credits from earlier...
We got a new type of credit.
It's called a pollution-free credit.
We've been using pollution credits.
Every time we use it, it causes pollution.
The pollution index goes up.
- Then...
- Gosh.
we used a total of 15 credits so far.
I think it's at 15
because we used 15 credits in total.
- Vector didn't use any credits.
- I used zero credits.
Counting the number of trades
from Days 1 and 2,
- we would've used 6, 3 credits each day.
- Yes.
Each team used one credit...
- for the quiz today.
- Okay.
Let's say we used some credits for hints.
So the pollution index matches
the total number of credits...
used so far.
Anyway, it's at 15 now.
Once we hit 100,
- the skull will be colored in red.
- Yes.
- What we heard was quite terrifying.
Once it reaches 100,
there will be massive damage...
to everyone's assets
in the Community Town.
Damage to our assets?
We were told that it could incur losses...
- on everyone's assets.
- Oh, my gosh.
(During the resource collection)
It could result in critical damage...
to the safety and assets of everyone
in the Community Town.
That's why
when we were doing our mission today,
we were able to change our credits
to pollution-free credits.
When you did,
how was the ratio?
It was half.
So our credit production...
will go down by half from here on out.
(Regular credits: 3)
(Pollution-free credit: 2)
(Maillard lowered the yield ratio
than the actual yield ratio.)
We heard that this pollution index...
would affect everyone's assets.
With the intention to prevent
as much pollution as possible,
we chose pollution-free credits.
If we choose pollution-free credits,
as you know,
the number of credits for all of us
would decrease.
Our opportunities
for productive activities would go down.
Then...
we should discuss whether or not...
we should get more pollution credits...
while keeping the number under 100
although it might be risky.
Or we should just go
with only pollution-free credits.
- We should...
- Here's the problem.
We don't have that many credits.
But we might not be able to
produce more credits tomorrow.
Here's the thing.
We didn't get to buy enough lives today.
It looks like all three teams...
will...
try to earn more lives tomorrow.
That means
there won't be any credits tomorrow.
Then we'll have a limited number
of credits the day after tomorrow.
And we'll still be short on lives again.
Yes. So this is...
a vicious cycle on repeat.
So that sums up our situation.
Maybe, this is like a test.
We can get more regular credits...
and use them until the index reaches 100.
I mean, we can do that.
For communal interests,
we have to be less selfish.
Will we be able to keep the index
below the threshold?
With this announcement,
there are more things my team can do now.
My team can use...
regular credits,
and we can use a lot of them...
while selling pollution-free credits.
I wanted to use the new system
with pollution-free credits.
The leaders at today's negotiation...
were quite innocent.
They believed me.
I exaggerated a bit to scare them.
They took everything I said at face value.
I thought, "This is nice."
- Until tomorrow...
- Then the pollution index...
Let's say
there's another negotiation tomorrow...
- and we discuss the pollution index.
- Okay.
- We used up all of our regular credits.
We have to check
how much the index goes up...
- based on the credits your teams use.
- Right.
- We have to check that.
- Yes.
- We only have regular credits.
It'd be nice to check the index tomorrow.
Next, there are two items on the agenda
that require your decisions.
- The first item on the agenda.
- Okay.
Providing a life
to open the supermarket the next day.
To pass this item,
the majority must stand in agreement.
The team providing the life must agree.
Any transfer of resources
executed without negotiation...
or outside the Trading Station...
will not be recognized by the system.
Please keep this in mind.
Discuss whether or not
you would provide a life...
to open Black's supermarket the next day.
Once the negotiation reaches an agreement,
say, "Negotiation complete."
- Let me explain this.
- Okay.
It's impossible for me to make any trades.
There's no possible way
for me to obtain a life.
I've tried all kinds of things.
Life acquisition outside the system...
won't be recognized.
It means I won't be able to use
the life I acquired today.
The announcement said
any resource acquisition...
executed outside the system
wouldn't be recognized.
Since I traded on the black market,
it was done outside the system.
"So this isn't mine."
So many thoughts
were going through my head.
"Should I return this? What do I do?"
Only during the Leader Negotiation,
you can provide me with one life.
And it's only possible with your agreement
since you hold the lives.
I think that sums it up.
I'd be really grateful
if you agree to give me one life.
I know that
each life is incredibly precious.
If you decide not to provide me with one,
I won't resent you for it.
However, if you don't give me a life,
the supermarket tomorrow...
- It won't open?
- It won't open at all.
- You can't open it.
- Actually,
it's a huge financial loss for me.
I'd like to remind you that
after another exhausting day,
everyone will get hungry...
and be on edge while playing games.
I think going without food for one day
might not be a bad idea.
If the majority agrees,
I don't have to make money for a day.
Given the circumstances,
I decided to pretend that
I was putting the community first.
"I'll sacrifice my profits."
"You should protect your lives."
I won't hold it against you...
if you disagree.
I have a question.
- On Day One,
- Yes?
they didn't give you any life?
- They only gave me one. Yes.
- Is that so?
But you need to keep
running the supermarket.
I just assumed that you were already
given the lives you'd need...
to run the supermarket until the last day.
- I was flustered that I only had one.
- But if that's not the case...
On Day One, we were informed that...
there were 43 lives.
The distribution of the lives
isn't what we had in mind.
- If you don't have any lives with you,
- He's right.
the numbers don't add up.
One of the teams
is holding onto a lot of lives.
I'd like to point out that
I don't have any lives with me.
Once the supermarket
doesn't open tomorrow,
that should confirm it.
I don't see
how else I can prove this to you.
- Okay.
(At this rate,
everyone will have to starve.)
Actually, the only team
that can afford to give a life...
is Team Blue. But you guys...
are short on lives. Right?
So it's not easy to give away one life.
Right?
Yes.
Here's the thing.
With all due respect,
the current value of lives
is far too great.
To tell you the truth,
even our perspectives are not aligned.
- My team is divided too.
- Okay.
So before coming here,
I told them
I wouldn't commit to anything...
- we didn't agree on first.
- I see.
Well,
it looked like we were the only team
that could afford to provide a life.
If the supermarket closes,
no one will be able to eat any food.
Hunger drives people crazy.
Then I thought
there could be more incidents...
that might expose my team to danger.
"Should I just give him a life?"
"Should I just give him one..."
"and tell the girls to deduct one
from my share?"
"What do I do?"
I knew that both of them
would be dead set against this idea.
I could hear Genie's voice.
I could hear Pitou's voice too.
"Why would you do that?"
"We can just starve."
I can hear their voices,
talking like this.
(Salt, Writer)
It's too valuable.
I'm the leader.
But I made a promise to my team
before coming here.
I'm not sure...
if I can just make this decision
without running it by my team first.
- You're the leader.
- This is...
You don't need their permission.
It's...
If you insert only one of these later,
you won't need their permission. Right?
He's a scary one.
You must know that leaders have
this power over them.
At the end of each day,
if you insert a life...
only under your name, only you'll survive.
Then you won't need more lives.
So do you really need their permission?
I mean, you brought it up.
I understand that
you represent your team.
- But you're here...
- Right.
as their leader.
I do think as a leader,
you have to make these tough decisions...
and be able to use your power.
I understand your point very clearly.
- Wait. I'm not following.
- Yes.
Is it possible for the leader...
to stay on without holding any life?
No. If there's only one resident left
in the team,
you don't need any lives after that point.
- Right.
- Yes.
So it's when we insert the lives.
- I see. There's a way you can kill off...
- If you don't insert...
- the other residents?
- Right.
Every leader has that power.
It's just that no one has done it so far.
Currently,
this is the only power leaders have.
My heart is pounding.
So...
- let's say I insert only one life today.
- Yes.
Then...
- The other two will get eliminated.
- It doesn't...
It doesn't matter what remains?
- Right.
- They'll get eliminated?
- Right. They must leave.
- That's right.
- The submission finalizes it.
- Then...
the role of a leader
became so important starting today.
- Yes. It's always been important.
- It was important yesterday too.
- No. This changes everything now.
- I see. She didn't tell you yesterday.
- Considering...
the personalities of my teammates,
there will be a lot of changes
based on who takes the position of leader.
You didn't know about this.
Genie didn't tell us...
that if I submitted my life only,
I could be the only one to survive.
I don't remember her telling us.
I never imagined
that could even be possible.
The biggest thing I've realized
about being a leader...
is that I could kill everyone
and survive on my own.
In such a situation,
Genie could easily kill me...
if she wanted to.
So if there's someone you think...
could be a threat...
to you being re-elected tomorrow,
you'd need to talk...
to the other person in advance...
for the sake of your survival.
We all know...
that the lives are running out.
This place is really scary.
- It's really scary.
- You have to think carefully.
The leaders...
can kill their own members.
- Of course.
- That's right.
Of course.
Being the leader is quite scary.
But we won't do that.
There are people who can do it.
That's right.
We'll see such people soon or later.
They'll try to become the leader.
I hope Team Blue's leader
doesn't get changed to Genie.
I can persuade Salt.
She doesn't seem to have much will
to exploit the authority.
That's why I kept saying
I wanted Salt to be the leader.
I thought someone in Team Blue
will soon get to die.
It looked like the members weren't
on the same page yet.
I hope Salt survives the longest.
She's the easiest to trade with.
(Exclaiming)
Should I kill her?
Would she try to kill me if I kill her?
What should I do?
I'm most scared of Genie.
Our opinions are different.
It's so clear...
that she puts herself first.
She's a transparent person.
Since she's so transparent,
I can tell that
I could always be in danger...
if she goes by her standard.
She's like an early warning.
- Shall we move on to the second item?
- Yes.
It looks like we've settled the agenda.
It seems like Team Blue
won't be providing any lives today.
You won't be running
the supermarket tomorrow.
That's right. I'm jobless.
The negotiations have failed.
The supermarket will close down tomorrow.
Moving on to the next item on the agenda.
I should have stored a lot earlier.
Tomorrow,
we should have eggs and bananas...
- That's right.
- for breakfast.
(Exclaiming)
Our impoverished...
We're poor.
We can spend some.
- Let's eat well tomorrow.
- Okay.
The second item on the agenda.
This concerns the decision
to provide aid or impose sanctions.
First is aid.
If a majority of the leaders agree,
resources currently in their possession...
may be transferred between two teams...
without spending any credits.
Next is sanctions.
If a majority of the leaders agree,
one team will be prohibited from using
the Trading Station for the following day.
Only one of the two options,
aid or sanctions, can be implemented.
If no agreement is reached,
the negotiation period will end.
- Sanctions.
- Once the negotiation is complete,
please say, "Negotiation complete."
That's stopping a team
from making any trades, right?
There's no benefit to the community.
So far, that's right.
Is it a must to choose one of the options?
No, we can decide to choose none.
- We can decide to choose none.
- Right?
And if we are to choose,
we can only choose one of them.
We can only choose one of those options.
Will this item come up every day?
I think so.
I think the second item came up...
to tell us that we could provide aid...
or impose sanctions.
It's hard to make a decision today...
since we didn't know anything about this.
- That's true.
- No team needs aid now, right?
We don't really need aid right now,
- but I'm sure the need will come up.
- Tomorrow...
Also, about what I mentioned earlier,
- in your rooms...
- That's right.
There's a code
on the wall with the TV, right?
- Yes.
- We have one.
I'm really curious to know what's there.
If there are lives there,
I think we should break it.
I don't think we can get lives...
only through productive activities.
- That's right.
- In that case,
even if Teams White, Red, and Blue...
answer all the questions right,
we can't coexist...
- with this number.
- That's right.
Let's talk about this outside.
I think we should quickly
solve the codes in our room...
and make those resources communal.
Are you sure
they're resources in the first place?
We don't know. But to just do nothing,
the pressure is closing in on us quickly.
So I want us to find more resources.
The resources we're mining...
aren't enough.
- We already solved it.
- Really?
We solved it the day we got here.
We solved it in 30 minutes
the day we got here.
We're wondering if all the other rooms...
have the same code.
Is it a code
that has to be brought together,
or does everyone have the same code?
That's our question.
If it's the same code,
we'll try to find more resources...
with the solution we got.
If not, I'm saying this
to change the way...
of finding resources.
I'm curious about your codes.
If any team is willing
to share it with us,
we'll try to share the resources...
we get out of it...
with that team.
We'll try to make that happen.
If it's the code you're talking about,
I think I can share it with you
using my authority as the leader.
Then we can do that after this ends.
- We can do it outside...
- Yes.
- if that's possible.
- I'll share it with you.
All right.
I'm doomed.
If there are three leaders,
they'll most likely agree.
How can I say no to that?
I'll be discovered right away
if they worked together.
I tried to keep a straight face...
and thought, "I should try
to win them over after the meeting."
This is the biggest crisis of my life.
Then...
- Negotiation failed.
It's so scary.
- All negotiations are complete.
- Okay.
We'll move on to today's life submission.
Who's going to start?
- I'll go last.
- I'll go first.
Sure. Go ahead.
It's so scary.
I've got chills.
I don't know what to do.
You have to protect your power.
Think about it. You won't...
submit 2 lives when you have 3.
You shouldn't let someone
who could do that become the leader.
I didn't think about that...
when Pitou was the leader.
But...
You think it'll be a bit risky
when Genie becomes the leader?
I think there's a possibility.
(Dormitory for Blue)
- Genie.
- Yes?
Do you think...
we can survive?
You're suddenly worried about that?
Suddenly...
I really like this peaceful state.
I want to do better since we're a team.
Right.
You feel more responsible.
It certainly feels different...
compared to when I played it by myself.
But you still have plenty of lives.
So far, yes.
You might get your turn again.
But everyone's standard
of "plenty" is different.
Of course.
Your life submission is complete.
You may now leave.
(Everyone in Team Red survives Day 2.)
You can get re-elected through voting.
That's right.
That way, you can keep your power.
I'm done.
- Well done.
- I think I could do it through voting.
- For now...
- Go ahead.
After Pitou,
it was to be decided through voting.
- What is it?
- They decided to take turns...
- being the leader.
- I see.
Please check the contents
of the central box...
and assign lives
to the residents of your choice.
Okay.
(Life Submission for Day 2)
I'm so nervous.
(Salt, Pitou)
(Salt, Genie, Pitou)
Today's my chance.
(The Community 2: Invisible Hand)